const quizQuestionsBands =[
    {
        question : "Who was the lead singer for Queen?",
        a: "Robert Plant",
        b: "Freddie Mercury",
        c: "George Michael",
        d: "Seal",
        correct: "b",
    },

    {
        question: "Where does the popular band A-ha come from?",
        a: "Sweden",
        b: "Denmark",
        c: "Norway",
        d: "England",
        correct: "c",
    },

    {
        question: "What was Prince' best selling album of all time?",
        a: "Purple Rain",
        b: "1999",
        C: "Around the World in a Day",
        d: "Emancipation",
        correct: "a",
    },

    {
        question: "How many records have Boni Jovi sell worldwide?",
        a: "40 million",
        b: "50 million",
        c: "74 million",
        d: "130 million",
        correct: "d",
    },

    {
        question: "What are the names of Van Halen brothers?",
        a: "Johnnie & Freddie",
        b: "Alex & Eddie",
        c: "Ben & Jerry",
        d: "Jordan & Larry",
        correct: "b",
    },

    {
        question: "Where was band U2 formed?",
        a: "London",
        b: "Dublin",
        c: "Cork",
        d: "Liverpool",
        correct: "b",
    }
]

const quizQuestionsLyrics = [
    {
        question: "Is the the real life __________?",
        a: "Is this just magic",
        b: "Is this just fantasy",
        c: "Is this just mercury",
        d: "Is this just landslide",
        correct: "b",
    },

    {
        question: "Ah, can't you see what I mean__________?",
        a: "Ah, might as well jump",
        b: "Might as well lump",
        c: "Might as well stop",
        d: "None of the above",
        correct: "a",
    },

    {
        question: "I never meant to cause you any sorrow__________?",
        a: "I never meant to cause you and gain",
        b: "I never wanted to be your main",
        c: "I never meant to cause you any pain",
        d: "I never ever want to see you again",
        correct: "c",
    },

    {
        question: "With or withour you_____________?",
        a: "I can't live",
        b: "I can't breathe",
        c: "I can't be",
        d: "I can't even",
        correct: "a",
    },

    {
        question: "We've got each other and that's a lot for love We'll give it a ____?",
        a: "jump",
        b: "life",
        c: "shot",
        d: "magic",
        correct: "c",
    }
]